Feroz Khairy

Glendale, AZ | (602) 607-8265 | feroz.khairy000@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/feroz-khairy

Summary of Qualifications

- Bilingual in Persian and English
- Experience working in customer service and collaborative/team-oriented environments
- Proven time management and adaptability skills
- Eagerness to learn and ability to learn quickly
- Communicate effectively with people

Technical Skills

Software: Microsoft Office, Google Suite, Adobe XD, Figma **Programming Languages:** Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Frontend Frameworks & Styling: Bootstrap, Tailwind, CSS Flexbox, CSS Grid

Tools & Platforms: Git, GitHub, Netlify, Agile (Project Management)

Operating Systems: Windows, macOS, Linux

Education

Glendale Community College- Glendale, AZ

August 2023- Present

Associate in Applied Sciences in Information Technology

Bakhtar High School- Mazar-e-sharif, Balkh, Afghanistan High School Diploma

June 2017

Training and Certification

Agile (Project Management), Certificate of Completion, Udemy, Completed: February 2023 CSS Grid (Responsive Website), Certificate of Completion, Udemy, Completed: December 2022

Experience

Walmart- Phoenix, AZ

June 2023- December 2023

Stocker

- Work with highly diverse customer populations and assist with answering questions
- Utilize organizational and time management to complete tasks in a high-volume, fast-paced environment
- Work collaboratively and cooperatively with peers to increase efficiency and maximize workflow

Rana TV- Mazar-e-Sharif, Balkh, Afghanistan

February 2017- October 2021

On Air Management

- Collaborated within a team to create and manage broadcast schedules
- Assisted with ensuring viewers saw high-quality content that aligned with the network's goals and standards
- Worked with Adobe Premiere Software to add video effects and edit videos of footage taken out on the field to air on television channels
- Worked with others to help oversee and coordinate various aspects of on-air broadcasting, ensuring the smooth and effective execution of programs, content, or broadcasts

Academic Projects

Portfolio: https://ferozkhairy.dev

Additional Skills

- Networking Basics: Knowledge of basic networking concepts, including TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, and Wi-Fi connectivity troubleshooting
- Software Installation and Configuration: Ability to install, update, and configure software applications
- Hardware Maintenance: Basic hardware maintenance skills, including installing RAM, graphics card, hard drives, and peripheral devices.